DANIEL TORRES CALVO

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Costa Rica

PHONE

8587-2400

EMAIL

daniel.torres96@hotmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

27/04/1996

DRIVING LICENSE

B1

LINKS

LinkedIn

Portfolio

SKILLS

Teamwork

Communication

Adaptability

Proactive

Self-motivation

LANGUAGES

Spanish

• • • • •

English B2

• • • • •

HOBBIES

Movies

Beach

Read

Music

Travel

PROFILE

Experience building web applications. With knowledge about user interfaces, testing, and debugging processes. Proficient in an assortment of technologies including Java, JavaScript, PHP and excellent experience of relational databases.

Able to work productively in a team in agile environments.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Developer, SysCo Consultores de Sistemas

Nov 2019 — Present

I work building customer facing web based applications. I have been working with custom development with Java Spring and technologies such as JavaScript, Maven and use of relational databases (Oracle). I gained experience building web services RESTful and code collaboration in teams using GitHub and SVN.

Able to implement solutions to existing projects according to the needs of the product owner.

Web Development Intern, Mouse Lamp Technologies

Jul 2019 — Nov 2019

I created a website developed in PHP with Laravel framework and I used the technologies JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, MySQL and GitHub. The website was develop for the sale of electronic products (e-commerce). Also has an administrative section for the control of products, inventories, orders and users.

Web Development Intern, Ministerio de Agricultura y Ganadería

Jul 2018 — Nov 2018

I worked with a team developing an activity management system and a reporting system in C#. We used ASP.NET Web Forms, Visual Studio Team Foundation Server and Microsoft SQL Server.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering, Universidad Nacional de Costa Rica

Feb 2019 — Nov 2019

Diploma's degree, Computer Programming, Universidad Nacional de Costa Rica

Feb 2014 — Nov 2018